{"status":"Success","data":{"quiz_datas":[{"question_no":"490","question":"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d","option1":"\u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d","option2":"\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7b\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d2f\u0d02","option4":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d31","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"584","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d - \u0d35\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u00a0\u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02","option1":"3214 K.M","option2":"3114 K.M","option3":"2933 K.M","option4":"38863 K.M","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"330","question":"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d06\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d4a\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d7d \u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d07\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d40\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ","option1":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u200c\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d34\u0d4d\u200c\u0d38\u0d4d","option2":"\u0d06\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7e","option3":"\u0d2b\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d3f","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"259","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d25\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","option1":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d02","option2":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02","option3":"\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 ","option4":"\u0d06\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d25","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"433","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d47 \u0d05\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d06\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ","option1":"\u0d10\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e","option2":"\u0d10\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e","option3":"\u0d10\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e","option4":"\u0d10\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"660","question":"\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d15\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ","option1":"1949","option2":"1946","option3":"1916","option4":"1911","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"659","question":"\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d2d\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30 \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d","option1":"\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d15\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d1a\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d47\u0d28","option2":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d57\u0d7a \u0d37\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c","option4":"\u0d07\u0d24\u0d4a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"661","question":"\u0d10\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d2d \u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37 \u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u200c \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 :","option1":"\u0d07\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d7d","option2":"\u0d07\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d32\u0d3f","option3":"\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28","option4":"\u0d1c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7b","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"463","question":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 :","option1":"2005","option2":"2006","option3":"2007","option4":"2008","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"354","question":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d","option1":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d02\u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d32","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d32","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d31","option4":"\u0d07\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d02","answer":"3"}]},"code":"100"}